reviewstream.com 2011-12-03

# REVIEW STREAM Privacy Policy

**ReviewStream.com Privacy Policy**

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

We work with the ad companies: 

\- Google Adsense   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

[Review Stream](http://www.reviewstream.com/ "Review Stream") Home
